{"test_questions": [[{"question": "\"Half-splitting\" is", "opta": "a means for nuclear fuel cells to produce electricity", "optb": "a means of isolating a problem in a circuit", "optc": "a means for reducing a high ac voltage to a low dc voltage", "optd": "a means of limiting current in a circuit", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If doubling the voltage across a resistor doubles the current through the resistor then", "opta": "the resistor value decreased", "optb": "the resistor value did not change", "optc": "the resistor value increased", "optd": "it is impossible to determine the change in the resistor value", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If the voltage across a fixed value of resistance is increased five times, what does the current do?", "opta": "It increases by a factor of five.", "optb": "It decreases by a factor of five.", "optc": "It stays the same.", "optd": "Not enough information", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If the resistance in a circuit with constant voltage increases, the current will", "opta": "increase", "optb": "decrease", "optc": "stay the same", "optd": "Not enough information", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the power in the given circuit?", "opta": "3.6 W", "optb": "35 W", "optc": "175 W", "optd": "245 W", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the kilowatt-hour consumption of a 40 W lamp if it remains on for 1750 h?", "opta": "43.75", "optb": "70", "optc": "43,750", "optd": "70,000", "ans": "B", "explanation": "(1,750 x 40)/1000 = 70 kilowatt-hour."}, {"question": "A damaged resistor", "opta": "may appear burned", "optb": "may have an increased resistance value", "optc": "may be checked with an ohmmeter", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Power supplies differ from batteries in that", "opta": "power supply output voltages are ac and not dc", "optb": "power supply voltages are not stable", "optc": "power supplies are low-current devices", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the resistor value in the given circuit?", "opta": "200", "optb": "1 k", "optc": "2 k", "optd": "4 k", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If voltage across a resistance doubles", "opta": "the current is halved", "optb": "the resistance doubles", "optc": "the current is unchanged", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the power in the given circuit?", "opta": "32 W", "optb": "80 W", "optc": "500 W", "optd": "16 kW", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Ohm's law describes the mathematical relationship between", "opta": "ohms, kilohms, and megohms", "optb": "resistor size and resistor value", "optc": "resistance, voltage, and current", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Energy is defined as the ability to", "opta": "produce heat", "optb": "produce light", "optc": "produce sound", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What electromotive force would cause 20 A of current to flow through a 500  resistor?", "opta": "0.04 V", "optb": "2.5 V", "optc": "25.0 V", "optd": "10,000 V", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The rate at which work is performed is called", "opta": "current", "optb": "energy", "optc": "power", "optd": "voltage", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A battery's capacity to deliver power is measured in", "opta": "kWh", "optb": "Ah", "optc": "Wh", "optd": "Vh", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Power supplies are regulated to prevent the output voltage from changing due to changes in the", "opta": "line voltage", "optb": "supply load", "optc": "frequency", "optd": "both line voltage and supply load", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the power in the given circuit?", "opta": "3.92 kW", "optb": "280 W", "optc": "28.6 W", "optd": "9.8 W", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If current through a resistance is halved", "opta": "the resistance is halved", "optb": "the voltage is halved", "optc": "the voltage doubles", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Ohm's law is a relationship between", "opta": "voltage, current, and time", "optb": "power, current, and resistance", "optc": "resistance, time, and current", "optd": "voltage, current, and resistance", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If the voltage in the given circuit was cut in half, what would the current equal?", "opta": "10 mA", "optb": "30 mA", "optc": "60 mA", "optd": "90 mA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}